Contact

+55 (11) 98428-1366 (Mobile) felipe.miyazato@usp.br

www.linkedin.com/in/felipe-gomes-miyazato (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

Data Analytics
Data Engineering
Mathematical Modeling

Languages

English (Professional Working)
Spanish (Native or Bilingual)
Catalan (Native or Bilingual)
Portuguese (Native or Bilingual)

Felipe Gomes Miyazato

Físico e programador

São Paulo, São Paulo, Brazil

Summary

I am a physicist graduated from IFUSP. I have been working for 5 years mainly with data analysis and engineering. Currently, I am directing my education towards working with data science. I am interested in research on machine learning applications.

Experience

Ali Crédito

Data specialist

January 2022 - August 2023 (1 year 8 months)

São Paulo, Brazil

- 1. Data owner
- 2. Data analysis and BI
- 3. Data mining
- 4. CRM management and modeling
- 5. Database management and modeling
- 6. Development and management of integrations, data pipelines and ETLs
- 7. Technical leadership
- 8. Developer of calculation engines for financial products
- 9. Code review
- 10. Cloud computing
- 11. Process automation
- 12. Operational support

GV2C Consulting & Solutions

Data Engineer

October 2020 - December 2021 (1 year 3 months)

São Paulo, Brazil

- 1. Automation and optimization project of accounting reporting systems
- 2. Remote teamwork
- 3. Project management and planning
- 4. Development of Python ETLs

Freelance

Data Miner

July 2020 - August 2020 (2 months)

São Paulo, Brazil

- 1. Data mining and consolidation of a database for scientific research
- 2. Self-management and resource optimization
- 3. Web-scraping with Scrapy, REST API and distributed data processing with Dask.

Predicta

Data Scientist

January 2020 - March 2020 (3 months)

São Paulo Area, Brazil

- 1. Python development, emphasis on integrations with GCP
- 2. Serverless Framework
- 3. Development of asynchronous ETLs
- 4. Google Big Query

TEVEC Inteligência Artificial

Data scientist

July 2018 - November 2019 (1 year 5 months)

Media Portal Soluções Software developer

January 2017 - March 2017 (3 months)

São Paulo, São Paulo, Brasil

Education

Universidade de São Paulo

Bachelor's degree, Physics · (2014 - 2020)